1549航班，清除起飛。
1549次航班，準備起飛
五月天，五月天，船長1549，它被打開
開業
沒有依靠電機2
船長1549，我們可以得到在跑道13期
我們不能做到，我們義無反顧地拉瓜迪亞
拉瓜迪亞大廈，1549航班我們將盡量使13
蘇利，我們是太低
蘇利，我們是太低了！
來吧！
它的設置著火了！
玷污
鸚鵡，我愛你！
到底是你怎麼了？
每個人，每個人都活了下來飛行1549！
你以為你會死，那是你的想法
然後，奇跡般地你不知道！
謝謝隊長，謝謝！
謝謝！
感謝您Sullbenger船長今天在這裡。
我也歡迎副駕駛斯基爾斯
很高興你在這一點上做到了。
藏漢不是像我們。
為了記錄在案，我們有一個飛機的系統調查，
而且飛機結構，MRT
飛機性能比較，ATCS，壽命的因素，生存因素
ND還應急今天我們開始
我們的運營，人力性能和調查。
美國1549航班墜毀
水降落。
隊長？
這不是崩潰，這是一個水上降落。
我們知道我們在試圖執行
這不是崩潰，這是一個被迫水上降落。
你為什麼不試圖返回拉瓜迪亞？
有根本沒有足夠的高度
哈德森是唯一的地方足夠的長度和光滑，足夠寬，能夠嘗試登陸。
空中交通作證說，你正在返回拉瓜迪亞，但你沒有。
當我開始左轉，
我意識到我不能讓它回來，我就已經消除了其他選項
返回拉瓜迪亞將是一個錯誤。
讓我們來看看你如何計算所有這些參數。
沒有時間來計算。
我一直依賴於我的過去四十年管理的航班千元的高度和速度體驗。
你說你沒有計算...
我嘗試。
- 您嘗試。
是。
最好的機會了乘客是這一點。
我敢打賭它我的生活。事實上，我做了！
而且我會再次這樣做。
航空工程師推論你有足夠的能量來回到跑道上。
工程師並沒有飛行員。他們錯了。
而且他們不存在。
無論如何，我們必須遵守所有影響作為調查的一部分。
我們的電腦analized方案
運行算法，具有精確的參數寫入模擬。
發動機損失，高度，一切你面對
當你做出你的決定。
我想監督這些計算機模擬
在調查過程中不可能的。
你這兒待它是一個雙引擎故障
由於鳥多次打擊？
這將是前所未有的！
一切都是前所未有的，直到它發生的第一次。
你是怎樣的睡眠是前一天晚上？
八個小時，就夠了。
這是可能的，血糖低？
我休息了，驚動了，完全知道我的周圍。
當你最後DRING，Sullenbenger船長？
九天前。
Droghe？
不，麥。
副駕駛斯凱爾斯？
我不喝酒，我從來沒有。
隊長，
你有過在家裡任何麻煩了嗎？
哦，不是比誰。
並沒有什麼，影響我的工作。
廢話。
但是，他們為什麼要找的東西，我們做錯了什麼？
這橫空出世的權利。
它沒有為航空公司和他們的保險公司橫空出世的權利。
我們應該期待一些反吹。
哦，像他們能說什麼？
我們不應該救的人呢？
這不是個人的。
The're只是在做自己的工作。
放鬆，平靜下來。
蘇利，他們應該給你一個金牌
送你回去工作。
對不起，此郵箱已滿。
我沒有叫洛瑞今天早上，我猜別人沒
沒有意思打擾，但我不得不說：
這是一種榮譽駕駛今天你。
謝謝。
到目前為止，有什麼新的說法嗎？二樓去了，
數百萬沒有工作，這是一月的第一個星期。
不過，今天的頭條新聞：
這很漂亮！
嘿邁克，我們為什麼不獲取驅動程序作為一個字符的見證？
最後。
哦，終於。
該航空公司已經給了我們被困一整天。
只是......我需要聽到你的聲音。
我heared其他人的。
你會驚奇地發現你有多少堂兄弟都有。
它沒有太多的感覺像家人一樣。
這是不是在這裡太安靜了。
有記者問的更新。
蘇利內部的頭腦。
洛瑞，告訴他們你不能談論。
我不能聽你的，只是叫我以後。
你不必與他們交談。
給我回電話。
你已經得到的消息？
你achiedeved不可能的事？
我覺得有一個汽車記者的。
自衛隊，認為陪審員將convinct？
你必須做的事情。
不，我所要求的權限。
警察會追你了。
蘇利你在做什麼？
薩利，你在聽我說話嗎？
我們應該再聊。
我一直在閱讀了一整天。
你還好嗎？
是啊，我只是累了，僅此而已。
怎麼樣的女生？
哦，好。
不堪重負了一下，聽起來好像你也有同感。
是啊，我會沒事的。
整個世界都在談論你。
蘇利，我不能相信這一點。
洛瑞，我得留在這裡，
待調查結束後，我告訴已經？
和我道歉，如果我沒告訴過你了。
你不需要道歉，你說的沒錯，你需要的人。
你知道，我沒有盡我所能。
當然，你做到了。
你救了大家。
也許我們應該講是在早晨。
我累了。
我對所有這些關注不堪重負。
我會在電視上第二天早上，他們會怎麼問我？
蘇利你要我來和你在一起？
沒有洛瑞
女孩子們需要你。
告訴他們我愛他們。
我愛你。
去睡一會。
是啊，也許我會醒來這將是1月14日。
那不是很好？
我愛你。
為什麼機長薩倫伯格所做的忠實決定將哈德森進入跑道？
好了，只有他能回答。
但是，我們現在知道，這是一個錯誤的選擇。
危及所有那些在船上的生活選擇。
因此，儘管該國大部分地區的稱讚他是英雄
這一新的信息肯定會改變對哈德森所謂奇跡的大家的理解
蘇利Sullenberger，你是英雄，還是一個騙局？
你好？
傑夫？對不起，給你打電話這麼晚。
這沒關係，有沒有在這個房間裡沒有睡覺無論是。
你能相信他們收取5元錢買了士力架？
我可以乘坐航空公司破產四個叮咬。
我想你可能想說話！ -絕對
讓我們得到一些空氣。
大
我將在那裡在5分鐘內。
享受震動？
惡夢？微弱的心跳？
一點點。該聯盟為我們提供咨詢。
是啊，你會說什麼？你是在一次飛機失事和生活。
它可能在你的日常產生影響。
我不喜歡在這個過程中的控制不是。
我贏了自己，
6個月內，我們會笑，因為我們知道大衛·萊特曼
我們正在做的大衛·萊特曼？
是啊，下周的面試後。
我猜大衛會激發你。
這是超現實如此。
我想我有在無論從任何地獄，這是現實分離的一些問題。
是啊，這是兩種人凍結他們的驢關閉
蘇利，別擔心，你做一個偉大的日子。
它會記住很長一段時間。
這裡有一個有趣的事：
我已經完成了超過一百萬人次超過40年在空氣中
但最終I'lm會被評為208秒
來吧，明天會是個好日子。
計算機將證明你是對的，你就會把你的翅膀回
你想運行？
是的，讓我們來運行。
冷他媽的在這裡。
這是顯而易見的，這是一個嚴峻的形勢
在低空失去兩個引擎
在地球上人口最多的地區之一
但是你選擇了降落在哈得遜，那仍然是一個大IF
我相信我能做到這一點
你之前是？
是。
你感覺如何時，人家罵你是英雄？
我不覺得自己是個英雄。我只是一個人誰在做他的工作。
正確的人選在合適的時間
你已經飛行了什麼呢？近40年？
42，那是我的生命
我的一生
飛機
炸彈工藝
我會很忙的兒子，讓你保持飛機乾淨吧。
他們是$每小時6認為這是一個課時
飛行員從來沒有停止收購knwledge。你會犯錯誤，大家都一樣。
不要忘了，不管發生了什麼，飛飛機。
當然，先生！
另外一個東西，這是很重要的！先生？
你可以微笑！
好的！
我為我出汗道歉。
哦，不，畢竟你沒有，我不認為凱蒂可能更嚇人
哦，那不是凱蒂，這是光，你把相機。
好吧，我們就大功告成了。
這是從我的媽媽。
她叫布倫達，她告訴我說謝謝，她是單身！
好吧，告訴布倫達謝謝你，但我在家裡有一個女孩。
幸運的女人
蘇利，SULLY！
薩利，你在哪裡？
我站在這裡呼喚你的名字。
你怎麼了？
你需要得到關注，因為媒體請求雪崩繼續。
是啊。
拉裡·魯尼主動請纓跳和運行獵槍的方式休息
想你可能需要一個朋友。
他會帶你到現在NTSB。
空中客車完成計算機模擬藏漢
好，好，這將幫助！
還有別的東西
所謂辦事處，左發動機仍在運行
不可能的，我覺得它走了。這就像它在半空中停止。
他們說，有一個機會，這是亞空轉。
我只是讓你知道，因為NTSB已經這樣做。
你一定是在開玩笑吧。
我們的工作是調查。我們的飛機在哈得遜河結束了。
是不是有點早了，你去釣魚？
搜索事實是不完全去釣魚，老八先生，
讓我們來看看最重要的事實：當時只有兩個人誰知道發生了什麼
在這一天的駕駛艙，我就是其中之一。
非常感謝您的觀點。
今天我們為什麼在這裡？
是不是因為Sullenberger機長沒有返回拉瓜迪亞？
看在AR320，我剛剛完成訓練，我可以告訴你飛機操作如此出色的唯一理由
是因為船長的輔助動力裝置開啟
他只是跟著QRH
不，不，他不是。他沒有按照正確的步驟都沒有。
我知道，因為我已經在我手中QRH。
他反吹發動機後，立即切換到APU。據空客這是做第15件事。
如果他跟著該死的規則，我們就死定了。
也許這就是你不喜歡的部分。你必須回答您的猜測
你看，他只是說，我拿著它做什麼和它做什麼做AR320
我拿著死者的飛行員recountless CVR成績單和我有顯著事故調查的經驗。
毫無疑問，你是一個有才華的，敬業，經驗豐富的專業。
調查之前每次崩潰不是本次調查的對象。只有今天美國航空公司1549事宜。
你的工會已被告知，該數據涉及了左發動機繼續飛行過程中設置自己。
那麼數據是錯誤的
有證據表明，該引擎是空閒或子空閒立即鳥擊以下。
你給我看左邊的發動機，我告訴你死禽和無動力
左發動機失去了在事故中，由於對著陸過多的損害。
稍後我們會繞回了，
我們只是假設，就像你說的，雙引擎的損失。
你的體重是151.510磅，風力和溫度，秦皇島港，西北方，21度，速度和高度200點頭2818英尺。
正確。
美國航空公司1549航班的計算機模擬表明，航空工程師是正確的。
有足夠的速度和高度的鳥擊的成功的返回拉瓜迪亞後
成功的？
飛機降落在拉瓜迪亞機場完好，無損壞。
你說從一台計算機模擬？
不，20。
包括從拉瓜迪亞機場跑道上作出努力。每台計算機模擬與精確飛行參數
表明返回拉瓜迪亞機場是可能的。而且不只是可能，很可能。
是否有人在這裡需要進一步的計算機證據？
Sullenberger隊長？
副駕駛斯凱爾斯？
這次不行。我想去過來的參數。
我們將使其可用於聯盟。
而一旦調查完成後，我們將能夠分享實際的計算機模擬
現在，他們仍然是保密的。我們不能洩露給新聞界。
已經有對新聞界已經太多交談。
當完整的駕駛艙語音編譯，旁邊帶有板載成績單，我們會打電話給你。
謝謝您們。美好的一天。
謝謝。
我們不是在玩吃豆人，我們開飛機的人。
其他的一些，則要記住它。這只是看起來不正確
這是因為這是不對的你所做的一切你可以，那是綽綽有餘。
問問你的乘客，問問你的妻子和孩子。問洛瑞
那麼，什麼是你從駕駛艙聽到的第一件事？
佈雷斯衝擊
現在，聽說過，以前？
不，其實也沒什麼
聽說過，在你生活的任何方面？
就拿本次車展離我而去。
傑夫是輕鬆和精緻。他應該得到比其他請求。
難道他們付你？對於所有這些媒體的東西，至少？
沒有付款是必要的。
哦，我希望銀行有同樣的感覺
為什麼？你什麼意思？
這只是....我們有另外一個通知。
關於查看縣的空間。
好了，我們會找到一個租戶。它只是需要時間。
你已經說了9個月，蘇利它仍然空缺
經濟已經轉一轉。
這感覺就像，如果我們失去了空間，接下來的事情將是房子。
洛瑞，我們不會失去房子。
對不起。
我很抱歉，我只是著急，獨自睡不夠。
是啊，我沒有得到足夠的睡眠無論是。
對不起增加你的壓力，但是，只要告訴我，你很快就會回來。
那麼直到NTSB已完成調查。
我們需要你飛行。
洛瑞，如果出了問題，我的職業生涯，作為安全專家，將結束，為網站和名片。
我更擔心你的職業生涯作為試點。
如果我做這個打擊？
你在說什麼？
如果我做的事情錯了，結束我的職業生涯？
如果我所危及的那些乘客的生命。
蘇利，看新聞！
你是英雄！
而且每個人都會習慣它，包括國家運輸安全委員會。
第一種情況情景：NTSB列出我的可能原因。
這是直接退休，沒有退休金。
我的生命也就結束了。
好吧你現在嚇到我，薩利。這是怎麼回事？
左發動機可能仍然被閒置-ING。
而空客模擬說我仍然可以使人們回拉瓜安全。
但它沒有意義。
這是與一切討論中，我在駕駛艙的感覺。
那你為什麼這麼做玷污？
在水之地呢？這不是你可以做很多的危險的事情！
下午好。
金槍魚Vasel或天堂破碎。
金槍魚Vasel，很新鮮！
謝謝
今天太冷，太寒冷！
當你要和我一起去飛？
當美國航空公司開始飛往HIDRO酒吧。
我會談談，看是否能正常工作。
這是星期四！
皮箱已經塞滿禮物的意志。
總是有趣的獲得在機場的事。看來你旅行。
媽媽，他的轉向1.不要認為他能知道從哪裡傳來什麼禮物。
但我會。
也許一個雪球。
這是他會記得。一些來自紐約。
你忘了，當我們還是孩子？
好吧親愛的，我給你拿一個雪球了。
精細。來吧。
下午好。
隊長。
嗨，傑夫！我們不會做了！
我相信你此行，正好符合我們在門口好嗎？
高度表核實，3023。
3023。
清單完成。
你真的認為有凹陷？
檢查latests報告，我們可以把它一路夏洛特。
從牛排到弗裡斯科，在我身上。
我從來沒有been.And我聽到好東西
哦，大黃會打破你的心臟。
是的，我更喜歡小豬家的人。
小豬家就會停止你的心臟。
慢著，慢著慢著！
嗨，我很抱歉，精神給我們送來。我們註銷，你說你有個座位。
飛行是封閉的。
等待，看到那傢伙，看著那裡？
這是我的爸爸，這是一個緊急情況。他一定是在這次飛行。
好了，大家說的一樣。
高爾夫緊急情況。它是否去取消？
標識討好。
有多少行？ 3。
沒有在一起。我們會找到辦法的。
在這裡，我們去：22A，6A和6C
非常感謝！
很高興你來了！
你在6傑夫。哦，不，那是吉米，我會得到一些睡眠。
你要在這裡睡覺嗎？不敢靠近你。
喲，喲，晚安！
對不起，原諒我。
嗯，當然咯。
對不起，他喜歡拋開一切。這是完美的，我想趕一切。
昨晚我用Google搜索你。找到你的公司的網站。
這是令人印象深刻。謝謝。
我想我是一個很好的bullshitter，但你！你可以去臨！
只是在開玩笑，但你的網站沒有在3個國家擔心100名員工和總部
當更多的搜索，我意識到，這只是你。
現在，去方便。我剛剛完成它。
我從來沒有acused是一個bullshitter。
別誤會！這是一種恭維。
現在，該網站，我認識你！
下午好女士們，先生們，歡迎乘坐美國航空公司1549航班。
獲取一定要按照安全說明卡在你面前椅背，解釋THI飛機上的安全功能，為藏漢緊急出口的位置。
拉瓜迪亞，這是1549，準備過關
好了1549，128準備和保護。
獲得肯定把它們關掉。
只有一次我希望去拉瓜迪亞時間。
那麼你知道燙去拉瓜迪亞。
不，那是什麼？
飛在肯尼迪機場。
取出燃油品質驗證。
19000船上貨物。
船長的1549，跑道4，清除起飛。
船長的1549，清除起飛。
正鑽機
哈德遜河上的尼斯認為
我不能克服的是多麼的美麗在這裡了。
生活在空氣中更容易。
我想，這是。
鳥類！
媽的！
我很擔心，這是怎麼回事？
沒關係。
這可能是一個好主意，讓你的安全帶上。
我們有一個滾動回來。
我們有回滾。
點火啟動。
重新啟動APU。
只需仔細檢查你的安全帶吧。
安全帶。
你覺得它是什麼？我認為這是一個鳥擊。
我們不得不回頭來拉瓜迪亞。是啊。
走出QRH
我們失去了兩個引擎。
五月天，五月天這是船長1549，我們撞鳥了。
我們已經失去了兩個引擎，我們回頭來拉瓜迪亞。
好吧，你需要返回拉瓜迪亞？
左轉220。
你失去了哪個引擎？
在這兩方面，這兩款發動機。
湯，我有一個緊急情況。
什麼是報告？
這兩款發動機，這兩款發動機不見了。
拉瓜迪亞說去跑道13
塔，停止起飛，我們有一個緊急返回。 1549航班，鳥擊。
我們已經失去了兩個引擎，立即返回。
他失去了兩個引擎。
船長1549，如果你能得到一個觀點，你想嘗試跑道13的土地？
我們無法。我們將在哈德遜結束。
我有在河邊的A320潛水。鋁，棧拉瓜迪亞界外球。
讓我們把負載在塔吧。
我需要一個跑道，機長1549需要在機場拿到現在。
較新的塔，你是怎麼了？ 29號跑道準備。需要緊急降落？
是的，我會右側為Ftaburogh
拉屎。
這是隊長的支撐影響。
什麼？撐，撐，撐
低著頭，停留下來！
撐，撐，撐
船長1549，右轉至3-0。您可以在運行方式1 0降落了。
這是消極的，我們降落在哈得孫河。
對不起，再說一遍？
船長1549雷達失去聯繫。
IC，到這兒來。
我也得到了一個較新的副本凌晨2點左右，大約7英里。
船長1549，如果可以的話，你得到了跑道29可在??2點左右，7英里。
對不起帕特裡克。
不，他即將紐瓦克，他只是開箱。
Hook'em備份。
我們需要授權的消息。
注意所有飛機在JW附近，
我們看到，船號1549 ...低了哈德遜
我的目光在他身上
好了掛在直升機的視覺效果。
他在那裡。
他前往紐瓦克，7英里。只有7英里。
船長的1549，這是離港控制，防範，你看？
這是怎麼回事了
船長的1549，你看我嗎？
媽的，這是怎麼回事了！這會碰到水！
測試人員會降下來。
符合伊麗莎，它的標準。
他的聲音是那麼的平靜！
當他說，哈得遜，我也不會相信！
這沒有發生。
我們已經拿出了水上岸的倖存者，不是嗎？
擁抱
我還是走吧。
我很抱歉。我愛你。
是啊，我得走了。
選擇在哈德遜降落是一個巨大的IF！
有證據表明，回拉瓜迪亞機場是可能的。左發動機是亞空轉
這是美味11我有故障緊急迫降
收到。
看起來像水力學。
主席先生，我們需要迎頭趕上。
運行控制試驗。
我們需要更多的高度。
塔，這是微動11飛行控制
收到，左轉為2-2-0
無法
好了，繼續直行約2 1
2 1，非常感謝
2 1，增加速度
第一時間更新超清電影網
-= 字幕谷論壇 www.zimugu.com =-
一，你看看自由飛翔，沒有硝煙的痕跡
羅傑說2
我抄，我進近跑道21
繼你
我們要去0-2-0
好吧，你是自由的
美味11，檢查你的速度。
我再說一遍，保持控制。
避免失速。
1，檢查你的標題。你不會使跑道！
我知道了。
這是一個著陸先生的地獄！
沒想到我們要去做到！
我會開始收費這個東西，好嗎？
聽我說？
嘿，讓我知道你需要什麼。
電視：什麼似乎令人難以置信的是，在飛機上的所有乘客生還！
喂，是你嗎？
你是飛行員？玷污？這是你的，對嗎？
很高興見到你。
這是不真實的，你最後一天做了什麼。這是一個真正的高興見到你
我們得到了一個飲料後，只要我如願以償了。是不是啊曼尼？
是啊是啊，你這樣做！薩利！灰雁的拍攝，與水濺。
到1月15日！
每天最好的一年！
喂，彼得，蘇利在這裡，他的存在！
他是無處不在！
他是一個真正的英雄的男人！
滾滾而來，讓我們來看看他們是怎麼想！
沒有更多的人在船上帽，這就是它花費GW
好吧，謝謝。收到。
我們要進入市中心的子7。
我不能相信你不得不坐在地說。
我再說一遍，並沒有問題或猶豫。這是在棒球歷史上最好的圖片。
你撒謊湖人，是，它是什麼呢？或者是它的鬍子？
你只是嫉妒！
妒！？！
撐，撐！
低著頭，停留下來！
沒關係。
住了下來！
我並不想死！
撤離！
抓住你的救生衣，請
開門。
迷茫的尖叫聲....
每個人，出口是可用的。向前移動到離你最近的出口！
前進。在右邊有一個出口門。
爵士，撤離了飛機，現在！
冷靜下來，你會沒事的！
在這裡，這會是寒冷的外面。
跳！跳！
哦，我的上帝！
我們必須jump..no無需等待！
你能看到嗎？是啊
哦基督，這是一個平面。
五月天五月天，信道1-6，托馬斯·傑斐遜。我們在北川一客機！
我們在路線，我們會建議！
走吧，走吧！
吉米，傑夫還沒有得到出。我們不能讓他在那裡！
我們已經得到了他，我們已經得到了他！
他會好起來的！
繼續前進！
按照說明進行操作！
先生，先生！你能來幫我們？
大家繼續前進！
這架飛機的下來，我們上了翅膀乘客。
謹慎的做法
把毯子鋪在她的腿
你會沒事的蜂蜜，慢慢走
這個包裹在她的腿，使其緊。
它是如此寒冷在這裡。
開始來臨之際，我們快到了。
撿起來。
好的
3-2-1。這是很好的它的好！
就在那裡寶貝，加油。
一次一個。我們會得到大家！
我們讓他們的其他方式。
有點接近！
為36度的水的溫度和擋風玻璃-5
飛行1549倖存者從字面上設法活下去。
這裡爬起來，還有其他好心人來向右走，好嗎？
50碼，GO！
我會保護你這樣行嗎？好。
有人還在這裡，回來。幫我！
隊長！
隊長，我們得走了！
下班時間到了飛機，約吧！
好吧，讓我們去。走！
我會在後面。
蘇利，我們得走了！
每個人都好嗎？
所有這些奇跡般生還，他們發現300紐約人願意幫助他們
剩下的唯一問題是：會不會太晚了？
在曼哈頓鮑比庫扎，紐約一
來吧，給我你的手。來吧。
我確信我會死。
嘿，沒有人死亡的今天，好不好？
把你的手給我
你去那裡船長，這種方式！
給我你的手先生！
我們需要在這裡更多的毯子！
謝謝謝謝
是的，我們得到了他們！
你好？
我想打電話說我沒事。
哦，太好了，你還是遠離家鄉？
還有的是一個事件。我沒事，我只是莫名其妙地崩潰。
打開電視
你是什??麼意思，打開電視？
洛瑞我現在不能講，我會打電話給你當事情平靜下來。
我不得不降落在哈得孫河。
蘇利，我不明白
我愛你，我很好，告訴女孩，我行！
我得走了！
女孩打開電視
美國空運飛行後，廣泛的救援已經墜入哈德遜河。
哦，我的上帝。
把你的濕衣服脫掉，並包起來紅十字會。
你會沒事的。
傑夫！
玷污！
我需要一個損壞報告，我多麼嚴重，需要它吧！
155.這是我的電話號碼，那是乘客包括在內。
你怎麼樣？
我來回答這個問題的時候，你會算155。
好的，
我還活著。莎瑞，我簡直不敢相信我跟你說話。
船長，船長我在這裡給你護送到市長Bloomber和警察。
如果市長想打個招呼，他將不得不來這裡了。
蘇利，我拒絕與警察送你！
傑夫！我需要一個算！我們必須有一個算！
有沒有辦法給你一個計數。
讓我們將一個驅動器，你之前凍結。
隊長，市長和首席McKelly，來這裡見到你。
我不能，因為它是一個國內航班！
是的，我們毫不懷疑，但我們必須跟蹤乘客信息了。逐個！
好吧，我們可以幫助？
是的，我要打電話，讓你計數！
聽著，你已經做夠了。我願借此為您服務！
傑夫！
我很好。我在另一翼。
他們給我們帶來了澤西島！
我看不到你。我找不到你！
我能聽到你喊我的名字所有的時間。
我喊過，我不知道，我猜的河流....
你還好嗎？
我也愛你。
我們成功了！
飛機....飛機的墜毀！
在河上！
你在跟我開玩笑嗎？
噢，那是令人難以置信！
我從來沒有這麼高興在紐約我所有的生命！
嘿，貝蒂！
是不是你來嗎？
我猜他沒有聽到。
我在哈德遜船長失去1549。
好吧，我想你有急事，他沒有，一個王八蛋！
每個人都被拉開了！
這是一個奇跡！
我以為我失去了他們所有。
是我的乘客好嗎？
是的，110。
110.這不是好！
這是正常的，你是什麼意思這不是好？
別擔心，110是不同凡響！
如何Dureene？
Farly嚴重裂傷，但我們會繼續處理她的感染。
我敢肯定，他會沒事的。
有一個傷疤，一個故事的地獄告訴。
如果有人相信它，我現在看到它，我簡直不敢相信。
你降落在哈德遜河的飛機沒有劃痕...
Erny ...
該聯盟今天拉了所有的大槍...
你把一個該死的風險玷污。
有一個計數。
155？
這是官方的。
哦，155。
謝謝Erny。
嘿，卡爾！是？
玷污。卡爾。
你今天沒吹起來，是嗎？
我們在這裡，這是我所知道的時刻。
哦，這是可能會錯過，從酒店。
想有一個快字你。
這不會花費太多時間，先生們，這只能說
我們的員工致力於保護您的隱私。
如果有什麼需要，在所有...
如果可能的話，我想我已經清理均勻，並準備。
你在開玩笑嗎？如果我能我想給你這個整個酒店！
好了，好了謝謝艾拉。非常感謝你。
好了，任何東西玷污！
剛剛發生了什麼？
您剛剛通過一個完全陌生的擁抱。
阿來對蘇利！
當是你聽到有人在水面上登陸jetplane最後一次？
終於活了下來？
究竟。
我有剃鬚膏，刀片，兩對一些衣服。
你覺得我們是忍者？
這是在晚上七點鐘。你找到專賣品兄弟！
是啊。
玷污。
你還在做穿制服？
好了，我不知道。
你們看，這是一個漫長的一天。你為什麼不只是得到一些休息？
麥克將在這裡後，以確保你ok了！
謝謝卡爾。
不，謝謝隊長。
你知道，它已經一段時間，因為紐約有消息這麼好。
特別是隨著飛機。
以後我會看到你玷污。
這個詞的市府官員不斷重複....
當然飛行員的精確計時
船長蘇利Sullenbenger，該名男子誰幾乎沒有時間
成為所有時間的人。
嘿玷污，給我....
來吧，回答...
雙拼，CBR是2天。你能多快干涉？
玷污？
我知道空客對A320 manifacturer模擬，但下周的。
你可以讓他們重新安排？
在上午3？
我需要你做到這一點，在我們聽CBR。
櫃前完成。
為什麼？
我看到這些仿真的權利，我有一種感覺，與人類飛行員
而不是一台計算機，其結果將是不同的。
如果他們表現出什麼完全相同的結果？
如果他們這樣做，我就上吊英吋
這是關於定時拉裡的一切。你可以做到著急什麼。
肯定是地獄我同意這一點。
現在CBR是在週三，這是36小時。你能做到這一點？
我會盡力。我給了一個電話。
它已經晚了，所以你最好開始。謝謝拉裡。
嘿，鸚鵡
你好。我很抱歉打擾你。
親愛的，有什麼...發生了什麼？
我才意識到，有155人上飛機，而你是其??中之一
我們幾乎失去了你。
是的，但你沒有。我在這兒。
你是如何高舉？
請告訴我，這已接近尾聲。
這幾乎結束了。
好的。
我愛你。
我也愛你
我會打電話給你時，他們和我一起做。
早安玷污。
好吧，早安女士們，先生們。我的名字是查爾斯·波特
我已經從美國國家運輸安全，以便在今天進行這次聽證會分配
我們有很多的材料覆蓋。
但在此之前我們聽到駕駛艙錄音，我們會聽取了在第一時間與您紳士。
對於Sullenberger機長和聯盟的請求，空中客車公司已同意以查看飛行員模擬。
上傳鏈接，請。
這些模擬玷污，也不會改變的事情發生了那裡我的腦海裡。
鳥類！
1號是回滾！
自動駕駛的關閉。
飛行員關閉。
飛行指揮的了。
拉瓜迪亞機場，由於引擎故障，我們不得不返回
好吧，我要左轉到拉瓜迪亞機場3。
激活你的辦法。
活性。
13號跑道
讓我們坐下很好。
*報警*太低。
成功的降落在拉瓜迪亞。 13號跑道
備案：飛行員的和計算機的模擬取得了同樣的結果。
其次上傳請，有關第二輪？
鳥類。
給我3-1-0標題
標題3-1-0。
千。
太襟翼
襟翼了。
*報警*太低
成功的著陸，跑道19
多個機場，跑道，兩名成功的著陸
我們只是看到的計算機已經告訴我們。
很多腳趾，以設置這為今天被踩到。
但坦率地說，我真的不知道你的先生們通過玩遊戲。
現在我們可以認真的嗎？
隊長？
我們都聽說了計算機模擬，現在我們在看實際模擬，但
我不太相信。
你根本就沒有考慮到人的因素。
人類飛行員模擬表明，你可以使人們回機場。
不，他們沒有。
這些飛行員??的行為不像人一樣。就像誰是首次遇到這個人。
但他們提出了對像你這樣的反應。
鳥擊後立即，他們義無反顧機場。正確？
那是對的。
他們知道要找誰，並準確知道在哪裡飛。
他們沒有運行檢查，他們沒有打開APU
有所有你面臨同樣的paremeters。
沒有人警告我們。
沒有人說：你要在一個較低的海拔，任何飛機在歷史上失去兩個引擎。
但要冷靜，讓只是一個左轉到拉瓜迪亞像你回去拿起牛奶。
這是在2800英尺隨後立即水上降落的雙引擎虧損。船上155的靈魂，沒有人訓練了一個事件這樣。
沒有人！
在泰特波羅登陸，與unrealistick靠背角度，我們沒有發現鳥兒在那裡。
我想知道飛行員多少次的練習之前耍花招居然把它關閉。
我不是質疑飛行員，他們是很好的飛行員。
但他們明確指示了鳥擊後立即後腦勺機場。
你就沒有時間去分析這個決定。
在這些模擬你把所有的人類出艙。
多少時間做了飛行員不得不為這個事件做準備，這些模擬？
你要找的人的空氣。
然後使之人性化。
這不是一個視頻遊戲。
這是生命和死亡。
薩利的權利，這是值得幾秒鐘。
請讓練習者多少他們了。
17？
誰在泰特波羅降落飛行員有17個實踐的嘗試，我們剛剛目睹模擬之前。
你的反應決策時間為35秒。
35秒不是我們的時間。
我們只有208秒總讓....我要了。
上傳鏈接，返回拉瓜迪亞。
現在，我們增加了35秒的響應時間。
鳥類！
煤氣關閉。
35秒。
時間到。
開始了。
展望13。
我們正前方的機場。
*報警*注意，障礙
我們大約7英里遠。
*報警*地形！地形！
*報警*太低了！地形！
讓我們試試泰特波羅。
上傳的鏈接請。
鳥類！
飛行指揮了。
35秒。
引擎1和2的失敗。
讓我們看看，如果我們可以做到這一點。
太低。
*報警*障礙！障礙！
有沒有人需要看到更多的模擬？
現在我們看到的可能發生，我們可以聽一下我們實際上做了？
我們將著眼於在另一個日期其他結果。
伊麗莎白。
根據記錄，這是1549航班，2009年1月15日的CVR。
鳥類！
拉屎！
我們得到了一個滾動回
我們有兩個人回滾。
點火啟動。
走出QRH。
失去了發動機。
五月天五月天，我們失去了兩個引擎，我們正在轉向拉瓜迪亞。
好吧，你需要求助於拉瓜？左轉220。
你失去它的發動機？
在這兩方面，這兩款發動機。
檢查這些飛行點火。
點火？點火。
推力打火機。閒？閒。
船長1549你想嘗試跑道13的土地？
我們不能，我們正試圖降落在哈得孫河。
應急電源。應急發電機不在線。不在線。
船長的1549，這會是跑道31無法
好吧，你在哪裡需要降落？
你有10秒隊長。跟我說話。
船長1549，跑道4是可用的。
我不認為我們可以做任何的跑道。
凡是在新澤西，也許泰特波羅？
我馬上側泰特波羅機場。
拉瓜迪亞出發？有一個緊急入境。
船長1549他在機場馬上去。
你有緊急情況？
是啊，鳥擊，我能得到跑道1-1？
船長1549，想與泰特波羅試試？
*報警*障礙，障礙。拉起！
*報警*太低，地形！
這是隊長，支具衝擊力！
船長3-0 1549右轉。您可以降落在1-0！
我們不能做到這一點。
來吧，嘗試號碼1。
我們將在哈德森結束。
好吧，讓我們把襟翼下來，襟翼下來。
襟翼的情侶，想要更多？
不，這是很好的。
您在紐瓦克機場跑道了2-9，這會是2點左右，7英里。
你有什麼想法？
其實都不是。
我需要採取快速突破。
他們認為是什麼？
眼看我剛才做了什麼？
我會告訴你我的想法。
我只是這麼該死的驕傲。
你是在那裡，與所有那些分心。
我們這樣做在一起像一個團隊。
由於薩利。
我們做我們的工作。
好吧，我們必須讓這次聽證會回秩序。
你能解決嗎？
把你的座位。
這是說實話，我第一次是聽崩潰記錄。
同時與機長和副駕駛坐著實際。這是非凡的。
這是沒有模擬？
不，它不是。
先生們，我想告訴你，左發動機恢復。
我只是進行了全面的報告。
有發動機的風扇葉片廣泛損害，5壓縮機葉片均斷裂。
和8天線脈失蹤。
因此，沒有推力。
當你作證，它被完全摧毀。
該機的數據是錯誤的。
我想的東西添加到個人註釋：
我可以絕對的信心說，與其他船員溝通後
鳥類專家，航空工程師，跑步到每一個方案後，
運行的每個球員後，仍然有意外的結果..
它是你，Sullenberger機長，從數學方程去除你，只是失敗。
我不同意。
它不只是我，這是我們所有的人。傑夫，唐娜，新羅和Dureene。
和所有的乘客，救援人員。
和交通控制，直升機機組人員和水肺警察。
我們都做到了！
我們活了下來。
副駕駛老八，你有什麼想補充的嗎？
什麼，你會做不同的，如果你不得不再做一次嗎？
是的，我會在七月做到了！
字幕：Sergeddu
Flight 1549, Clear to take off.
Flight 1549, Ready to take off
Mayday, Mayday, Captain 1549,
It was opened
Opened
No rely on motor 2
Captain 1549,
We can get a view on runway 13
We can't make it,
We're turning back to La Guardia
La Guardia Tower, Flight 1549
We're going to try to make 13
Sully, We are too low
Sully, We are too low!
Come on!
It's  set on fire!
Sully
Lory I love you!
What the hell is the matter with you?
Everyone, EVERYONE survived on flight 1549!
You think you'll die,
that's what you think
And then, miraculously you don't!
Thank you Captain, Thank you!
Thank you!
Thank you Captain Sullbenger for being here today.
I would also welcome First Officer Skiles
Glad you made it at this point.
Not aswell as  we are.
For the record,
We have an aircraft system investigation,
and also aircraft structures, MRT
Aircraft perfomance, ATCS, life factors,
survival factors
nd also emergency response
Today we begin
with our operations,
human performance and investigations.
On the crash of US Flight 1549
The water landing.
Captain?
This was not a crash, it was a water landing.
We knew what we were trying to execute
It was not a crash, it was a forced water landing.
Why didn't you attempt to return to La Guardia?
There was simply not enough altitude
The Hudson was the only place long enough
and smooth enough and wide enough to attempt a landing.
Air traffic testified that you were returning
to La Guardia but you did not.
As I began the left turn,
I realized I couldn't make it back
and I would have eliminated other options
Returning to La Guardia would have been a mistake.
Let's get into how you calculated all those parameters.
There was no time for calculating.
I have relied on my experience on managing the altitude and speed
on thousand of flights over four decades.
You say you didn't calculated...
I attempted.
- You attempted.
Yes.
The best chance passengers had was on that.
And I bet my life on it.
In fact, I did!
And I would do it again.
Aviation engineers theorize you had enough energy to get back to the runway.
Engineers are not pilots.
They're wrong.
And they weren't there.
Regardless, we have to follow all implications
as part of the investigation.
Our computers analized scenarios
run algorithms, write
simulations with the exact parameters.
the engine loss,
the altitude, everything you faced
when you made your decision.
I would like to oversee those computer simulations
Not possible during the investigation.
You staid it was a dual engine failure
due to multiple blows with birds?
That would be unprecedented!
Everything is unprecedented, until it happens for the first time.
How much sleep did you get the night before?
Eight hours, enough.
It was possible that blood sugar was low?
I was rested, alerted, and completely aware of my surroundings.
When was your last dring, Captain Sullenbenger?
Nine days ago.
Droghe?
No, mai.
First Officer Skiles?
I don't drink, I never have.
Captain,
have you had any troubles at home lately?
Well, not more than anyone else.
And nothing that affected my work.
Bullshit.
But why are they looking for something we did wrong?
That turned out right.
It didn't turned out right for the Airline and their insurance company.
We should expect some blowback.
Oh like what they can say?
That we shouldn't have saved everybody?
That's not personal.
The're just doing their job.
Relax, calm down.
Sully, they should give you a medal
and send you back to work.
Sorry, this mailbox is full.
I didn't called Lori this morning, I'm guessing someone  else did
Not meaning to bother, but I have to say:
It is an honor driving you today.
Thank you.
What new have said so far? Two building went down,
Many millions without work, and that's the first weeks of January.
But today's headlines:
This is beautiful!
Hey Mike, why don't we get the driver as a character witness?
Finally.
Oh, finally.
The Airline has given us trapped all day.
It's just... I need to hear your voice.
I've heared everybody else's.
You'd be amazed how many cousins you have.
It doesn't feel much like family.
It isn't quiet here too.
There are reporters asking for an update.
Inside the mind of Sully.
Lori, tell them you can't talk.
I cannot hear you, just call me later.
You don't have to talk with them.
Call me back.
Do you've got any news?
Have you achiedeved the impossible?
I think there's the press with a car.
Self-Defense, think the juror would convinct?
Do what you have to do.
No, I'm asking for permission.
Cops will be coming after you.
Sully what are you doing?
Sully, are you listening to me?
We should talk later.
I've been reading all day.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm just tired, that's all.
How are the girls?
Oh good.
A bit overwhelmed, sounds like you are too.
Yeah, I'll be alright.
The whole world is talking about you.
Sully, I can't believe this.
Lori, I'll have to stay here,
Until the investigation is over,
Did I tell that already?
And I apologize if I didn't told you already.
You don't need to apologize,
You're right where you need to be.
You know, I did the best I could.
Of course you did.
You saved everyone.
Maybe we should just talk in the morning.
I'm tired.
I'm overwhelmed by all these attentions.
I'm gonna be on TV next Morning,
what are they gonna ask me?
Sully do you want me to come be with you?
No Lori
The girls need you.
Tell them I love them.
I love you.
Get some sleep.
Yeah, maybe when I'll wake up it'll be January 14th.
Wouldn't that be good?
I love you.
Why did Captain Sully made that faithful decision to turn the Hudson into a runway?
Well, only he can answer.
But we now know, it was a wrong choice.
A choice that endangered the lives of all of those on board.
So, while much of the country hails him as a hero
this new information will certainly change everyone's understanding
of the so called Miracle on the Hudson
Sully Sullenberger, are you a hero,
or a fraud?
Hello?
Jeff? Sorry for calling you so late.
It's ok, There's no sleep in this room either.
Can you believe they charged 5 dollars for a Snickers?
I can take the Airline to bankruptcy with four bites.
I thought you may wanna talk!
-Absolutely
Let's get some air.
Great
I will be there in 5 minutes.
Enjoying the shakes?
Nightmares? Little Heartbeat?
A little bit.
The Union is offering us Counseling.
Yeah, what would you say?
You were in a plane crash and lived.
It might have an impact in your day to day.
I don't like not being in control of the process.
I won myself that
Within 6 months we'll laugh about
as we know David Letterman
We're doing David Letterman?
Yeah, right after next week's interview.
I'm guessing David's gonna be excited for you.
This is so surreal.
I guess I'm having some problems in separating reality
from whatever the hell this is.
Yeah, this is two man freezing their asses off
Sully,
Don't worry, you did a great day.
It's gonna be remembered for a very long time.
Here's a funny thing:
I've delivered over a million passengers
over 40 years in the air
But in the end I'lm gonna be judged for 208 seconds
Come on, tomorrow it's gonna be a good day.
Computers will prove you're right,
and you'll put your wings back on
You wanna run?
Yeah, let's run.
Fucking cold out here.
This was obvious,
it was a critical situation
Losing both engines at a low altitude
Over one of the most populated areas of the planet
But you chose to land on the Hudson,
that was still a big IF
I was sure I could do it
You were?
Yes.
How do you feel when people call you a hero?
I don't feel like a hero.
I'm just a man who is doing his job.
The right man for the job
at the right time
You've been flying for what?
Nearly 40 years?
42, That's been my life
My whole life
Aircraft
Bomb-craft
I'll be busy son, so you
keep the plane clean please.
They are $ 6 per hour
Consider it a lesson time
Pilots never stop to acquire knwledge.
You'll make mistakes, everyone does.
Never forget, no matter what's happening,
to fly the airplane.
Absolutely, sir!
One other thing, and this is important!
Sir?
You can smile !
Alright!
I apologize for my sweating.
Oh no, After all you did I don't think
Katie could be more intimidating
Oh that wasn't Katie, It was the light
and the camera you brought in.
Ok, we're done.
That was from my mom.
Her name's Brenda,
She told me to say thank you and she's single!
Well, tell Brenda thank you,
but I got a girl at home.
Lucky woman
Sully, SULLY!
Sully, where are you?
I'm standing here calling your name.
What's up with you?
You need to get focused, because the media
requests Avalanche continues.
Yeah, yeah.
Larry Rooney volunteered to jump in and run Shotgun
with you the rest of the way
Thought you might need a friend.
He will take you to NTSB now.
AirBus completed computer simulations aswell
Good, Good, that will help!
There's something else
The Agency called,
The left engine was still operating
Not possible, I felt it go.
It was like it stopped in mid-air.
They said there's a chance it was sub-idle.
I'm just letting you know, since
the NTSB already does.
You've got to be kidding me.
Our job is to investigate.
Our plane ended up in the Hudson River.
Isn't it a little bit early for you
to go fishing?
Searching facts is not exactly go fishing,
Mr Skiles,
Let's see the most important fact:
There were only two people who know what happened
in the cockpit that day,
and I'm one of them.
And we appreciate your perspective.
Why are we here today?
Is it because Captain Sullenberger
did not return to La Guardia?
Look, I just finished training on the AR320,
And I can tell you the only reason the plane operated so well
Is because the Captain turned on
The auxiliary power unit on
He simply followed the QRH
No, no he wasn't.
He wasn't following proper procedure at all.
And I know because I had the QRH in my hands.
He switched to APU immediately after engine blowback.
According to the Airbus that's the 15th thing to do.
If he followed the damn rules, we would be dead.
Maybe that's the part you don't like.
You have answers to your guessing
Look, he's just saying that I held the AR320 what it does
and  what it does to do
I held recountless CVR transcripts of deceased pilots and I have
significant accident investigation experience.
There is no question that you're a talented,
dedicated, experienced professional.
Every crash investigated before are not object of this investigation.
Only US Airways 1549 matters today.
Your Union has been advised, The data relate that the
left engine continued setting himself on during flight.
Then the Data is wrong
The evidence showed that the engine was Idle or Sub-Idle
immediately following the bird strike.
You show me the left engine
I show you dead birds and no power
The left engine was lost in the crash,
due to excessive damage on touchdown.
We could circle back to that later,
Let's just assume, as you say,
a dual engine loss.
Your weight was 151.510 pounds, wind and temperature, nort, north-west, 21 degrees,
speed and altitude 200 nods and 2818 feet.
Correct.
The computer simulations of US Airways Flight 1549 showed that
the Aviation Engineers were correct.
There was enough speed and altitude after the bird strike
for a succesful return to La Guardia
Succesful?
The plane landed at LaGuardia intact, undamaged.
You got that from one computer simulation?
No, 20.
Including attempts made from LaGuardia runways.
Every Computer simulation with the exact flight parameters
demonstrated that return to LaGuardia was possible.
And not just possible, probable.
Does anyone here needs further computer evidence?
Captain Sullenberger?
First Officer Skiles?
Not this time.
I would like to go over the parameters.
We'll make them available for the Union.
And once the Investigation is complete,
we'll be able to share the actual computer simulations
For now, they remain confidential.
We cannot afford a leak to the press.
There has been far too much talk for the press already.
When the complete cockpit voice is compiled, alongside with onboard
transcripts we'll call you back .
Thank you gentlemen.
Good day.
Thank you.
We weren't playing Pac-Man,
we were flying a plane for human beings.
Some other, will have to remember it.
This just doesn't seem right
It's because this is not right
You did everything you could, that's more than enough.
Ask your passengers, Ask your wife and kids.
Ask Lori
So what's the first thing you heard from the cockpit?
Brace for impact
Now, ever heard of that before?
No, actually no
Ever heard of that in any aspect of your life?
Take this show away from me.
Jeff was relaxed and fine.
He should be getting over with other requests.
Are they paying you?
For all this media stuff at least?
No payment is necessary.
Oh, I wish the bank felt the same way
Why? What do you mean?
That's just....
We got another notice.
About the Space in View County.
Well, we'll find a tenant.
It just takes time.
You've been saying that for 9 months, Sully
It's still vacant
The economy has to take a turn.
It feels like, if we lose that space, the next
thing will be the house.
Lori, we're not gonna lose the house.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, I'm just anxious, and alone and
not enough sleep.
Yeah, I didn't get enough sleep either.
I'm sorry adding to your stress but,
Just tell me you'll be back soon.
Well not until the NTSB has finished
the investigation.
We need you flying.
Lori, If this goes wrong, my career as safety expert,
will end, as the website and the business card.
I'm more worried about your career as a pilot.
What if I did blow this?
What are you saying?
What if I did things wrong, closing my career?
If I endangered the lives of those passengers.
Sully, Watch the news!
You're a hero!
And everyone is going to get used to it,
Including the NTSB.
First case scenario:
the NTSB lists me as the probable cause.
That's immediate retirement, no pension.
My life is done.
Ok you're scaring me now, Sully.
What's going on?
The left engine might have still been idle-ing.
And the AirBus Simulations said I could still have made it back
to La Guardia safely.
But it doesn't make sense.
That's in discussion with everything I felt in the cockpit.
Then why did you do that Sully?
A land in the water?
That's not the much dangerous thing you could have done!
Good afternoon.
The Tuna Vasel or The Heaven Shatter.
Tuna Vasel, Very Fresh!
Thank you
Too cold today, too much cold!
When are you gonna come fly with me?
When U.S. Airways starts to fly to Hidro-Bar.
I will talk, see if can work.
This is Thursday!
Suitcase is already stuffed with gifts for Will.
Always fun to get things in the Airport.
Seems you travel too.
Mom, he's turning 1.
Don't think he can know what gift came from where.
But I will.
Maybe a Snow Globe.
Something he will remember.
Something from New York.
You forgot when we were kids?
Okay sweetheart, I'll get you a Snow Globe too.
Fine. Come on.
Good afternoon.
Captain.
Hey guys, Jeff!
We're not gonna make it!
I believed in you for this trip,
Just meet us at the Gate ok?
Altimeters verified, 3023.
3023.
Checklist complete.
You really think there are recess?
Checking the latests reports, We could
make it all the way to Charlotte.
From steaks to Frisco, on me.
I've never been.And I hear good things
Oh, Rhubarb will break your heart.
Yeah, I'm more like Porker House man.
Porker House will stop your heart.
Wait, Wait Wait!
Hi, I'm sorry, Spirit sent us.
We cancelled and you said you have seats.
Flight is closed.
Wait, see that guy, looking up there?
That's my Dad, it's an emergency.
He's got to be on this flight.
Okay, everybody say the same.
Golf emergency.
Did it go cancelled?
IDs please.
How many travelling?
3.
Nothing together.
We'll find a way.
Here we go: 22A, 6A and 6C
Thank you so much!
Glad you made it!
You're on 6 Jeff.
Oh no that's Jimmy, I'm gonna get some sleep.
Are you going to sleep here?
Not close to you.
Yo, yo, Goodnight!
Sorry, Excuse Me.
Yeah, of course.
I'm sorry, he likes to throw everything.
That's perfect, I like to catch everything.
I googled you last night.
Found you on the company's website.
That's impressive.
Thanks.
I thought I was a good bullshitter, but you!
You could go Pro!
Just kidding, but your site do not worry
about 100 employees and headquarters in 3 states
When searching for more, I realized that it was just you.
Now, go easy. I'm just getting it done.
I've never been acused being a bullshitter.
Do not misunderstand!
It is a compliment.
Now, with that website, I know you!
Good afternoon ladies and gentlemen, welcome on board
US Airways Flight 1549.
Get sure to follow the safety instructions card on seatback in front of you,
explains safety features on thi aircraft, aswell as locations of emergency exits.
La Guardia, this is 1549, ready for clearance
Ok 1549, 128 ready and protected.
Get sure to turn that off.
Just once I'd like to go to La Guardia in time.
Well you know hot to get to La Guardia.
No, what's that?
Fly at JFK.
Take-out fuel quality verified.
19000 Cargo aboard.
Captain's 1549, Runway 4, Clear to take-off.
Captain's 1549,  Clear to take-off.
Positive rig
Nice view on the Hudson
I can't get over on how beautiful is up here.
Life's easier in the air.
I guess, it is.
BIRDS!
Oh shit!
I'm worried, what's going on?
It's okay.
It might be a good idea to keep your seatbelts on.
We've got one rolling back.
We have both rolling back.
Ignition start.
Restarting APU.
Just double check your seatbelts please.
Seatbelts.
What do you think it was?
I think it was a bird strike.
We'll have to turn back to La Guardia.
Yeah.
Get out the QRH
We've lost both engines.
Mayday, mayday this is Captain 1549, we hit birds.
We've lost both engines, we're turning back to La Guardia.
Ok, you need to return to La Guardia?
Turn left at 220.
Which engine did you lose?
Both, both engines.
Soup, I have an emergency.
What's the report?
Both engines, both engines gone.
LaGuardia says go to runway 13
Tower, stop your departures, we've got an emergency returning.
Flight 1549, bird strike.
We've lost both engines, return immediately.
He lost both engines.
Captain 1549, if you can get a view, do you want to try land on runway 13?
We are unable. We'll end up in the Hudson.
I've got an A320 diving in the river.
Al, stack the inbounds in La Guardia.
Let's put a load in the Tower please.
I need a runway, Captain 1549 needs to get in an airport right now.
Newer Tower, what did you got?
Runway 29 ready. Need an emergency landing?
Yes, I'll be right side as Ftaburogh
Shit.
This is the Captain
Brace for impact.
What?
Brace, Brace, Brace
Heads down, stay down!
Captain 1549, turn right to 3-0.
You can land on run way 1 0 now.
That's negative, We're landing in the Hudson.
I'm sorry, say again?
Captain 1549, radar contact lost.
IC, come on over here.
I've got also a newer copy at 2 o'clock, about 7 miles.
Captain 1549, if you can, you got runway 29
available at 2 o'clock, 7 miles.
I'm sorry Patrick.
No, he's about to Newark, he's just out of the box.
Hook'em back up.
We need authorized news.
Attention all aircraft in vicinity of JW,
We see the USS ship...
1549, low over the Hudson
I got eyes on him
Ok
Hang on the chopper visuals.
He's out there.
He's heading to Newark, 7 miles.
Only 7 miles.
Captain's 1549, this is Departure Control,
On Guard, do you read?
It's going down
Captain's 1549, do you read me?
Shit, it's going down!
It's gonna hit the water!
Testers are gonna come down.
Meet Eliza, it's the standard.
His voice was so calm!
When he said the Hudson, I wouldn't believe it!
This isn't happening.
We have took out survivors on water landings, didn't we?
Embrace
I better go.
I am so sorry.
I love you.
Yeah, I gotta go.
Choosing to land in the Hudson was a big IF!
The evidence showed that a return to LaGuardia was possible.
The left engine was sub-idle
This is tasty 11
I have an emergency landing by breakdown
Roger that.
Looks like hydraulics.
Sir, we need to catch up.
Running a control test.
We need more altitude.
Tower, this is Tacy 11 with flight control
Roger that, turn left for 2-2-0
Unable
Okay, proceed straight for about 2 1
2 1, thanks a lot
2 1, Increasing speed
One, you look free to fly, no trace of smoke
Roger that 2
I copied, I approach runway 21
Following you in
We're heading 0-2-0
Ok, you're free
Tasty 11, check your speed.
I repeat, maintain control.
Avoiding to stall.
1, check your heading.
You're not going to make the runway!
I got it.
That was a hell of a landing sir!
Didn't think we were gonna make it!
I'm gonna start charging for this stuff, alright?
Hear me?
Hey, let me know if you need anything.
TV: What seems incredible is that
all passengers in the plane survived!
Hey, is that you?
Are you a pilot? Sully?
This is you, right?
It's a pleasure to meet you.
That was unreal what you did last day.
It's a real pleasure to meet you
We got a drink after you, as soon as that happened.
Ain't that right Manny?
Yeah yeah, you did!
The Sully! A shot of Grey Goose, with a splash of water.
To January 15th!
Best day in the year!
Hey Pete, Sully's here, and he's there!
He's everywhere!
He's a real hero man!
Keep coming, let's see how  they want!
No more people on board Cap,that's what it takes for GW
Alright, thanks. Roger that.
We're heading into Midtown in Sub-7.
I cannot believe you had to sat to say that.
I'd say it again, and with no question or hesitation.
It was the best picture in history of baseball.
Are you lying about the Lakers, is that what it is?
Or is it the mustache?
You're just jealous!
Jealous!?!
Brace, Brace!
Heads down, stay down!
It's ok.
Stay down!
I don't wanna die!
Evacuate!
Grab your life vests please
Opening door.
Confused screams....
Everyone, exits are usable. Move forward to your closest exit!
Move forward.
On the right there's an exit door.
Sir, Evacuate the plane right now!
Calm down, you'll be fine!
Here, it's gonna be cold out there.
Jump!
Oh my god!
We have to jump..no no Wait!
Can you see this?
Yeah
Oh Christ, that's a plane.
Mayday Mayday, Channel 1-6, Thomas Jefferson.
We have a passenger airliner in the north river!
We're in route, we will advise!
Let's go, Let's go!
Jimmy, Jeff has not got out.
We can't leave him there!
We've got him, We've got him!
He will be okay!
Keep moving forward!
Follow the instructions!
Sir, Sir! Can you come help us?
Everyone keep moving forward!
The plane's down, we got passengers on the wings.
Approach with caution
Put a blanket on her legs
You will be fine honey, go slowly
Wrap this around her leg, make it tight.
It's so cold out here.
Starting approaching, we're nearly there.
Pick it up.
Alright
3-2-1. It's good It's good!
Right there baby, Come on.
One at a time.
We'll get everybody!
We're getting them on the other way.
A little bit closer!
With a water temperature of 36 degrees and a windshield of -5
the survivors of flight 1549 literally have managed to live.
Get up here, there are other good people coming right away, ok?
50 yards, GO!
I'll keep you like that ok?
Ok.
Someone is still here, Come back.
Help me!
Captain!
Captain, We have to go!
Time to get off the plane, about now!
Alright let's go. GO!
I'll be right behind.
Sully, we got to go!
Everybody's okay?
All of them miraculously survived and they found
300 New Yorkers ready to help them
The only question remaining is: Will it be too late?
In Manhattan Bobby Cuza, New York One
Come on, give me your hand.
Come on.
I was sure I was gonna die.
Hey, no one dies today, ok?
Give me your hand
There you go Captain, this way!
Give me your hands sir!
We'll need more blankets over here!
Thank you, Thank you
Yeah, we got them all!
Hello?
I wanted to call to say I'm okay.
Oh good, are you still far away from home?
There's been an incident.
I'm okay, I just crashed somehow.
Turn on the television
What do you mean, turn on the television?
Lori I can't talk right now, I'll
call you when things calm down.
I had to land on the Hudson.
Sully, I don't understand
I love you and I'm ok, tell the girls I'm ok!
I have to go!
Girls turn on the TV
An extensive rescue after a US Airway flight has crashed into the Hudson River.
Oh my God.
Take your wet clothes off and wrap it up for the Red Cross.
You'll be okay.
Jeff!
Sully!
I need a damage report, how badly and I need it NOW!
155. That's my number, that's passengers included.
Ok, How are you?
I'll answer that question when you'll count 155.
Alright,
I'm alive. Shary, I can't believe I'm talking to you.
Captain, Captain I'm here to escort you to Mayor Bloomber and Police Officers.
If the Mayor want  to say hello,he'll have to come down here.
Sully, I refused to send you with a cop!
Jeff! I need a count!
We've got to have a count!
There's no way to give you a count.
Let's get you a drive before you freeze.
Captain, the Mayor and Chief McKelly, come down here to meet you.
I can't, because it was a domestic flight!
Yeah, we have no doubts, but we have to track the passengers informations down.
One by one!
Ok, can we help?
Yeah, I'm gonna call and get you a count!
Listen, you've done enough.
Let me take this for you!
Jeff!
I'm okay.
I was on the other wing.
They brought us to Jersey!
I couldn't see you.
I couldn't find you!
I could hear you shouted my name all time.
I shouted too, I don't know, I guess the river....
Are you okay?
I love you too.
We made it!
The plane.... the plane's crashed!
On the river!
Are you kidding me?
Oh, that's unbelievable!
I've never been so happy to be in New York in all my life!
Hey Betty!
Ain't you coming?
I guess he didn't hear.
I lost Captain 1549 in the Hudson.
Yeah, I guess you had a hurry, he hadn't, the son of a bitch!
Everyone's been pulled off!
It's a miracle!
I thought I lost them all.
Are my passengers alright?
Yes, 110.
110. That's not good!
It's alright, what do you mean it's not good?
Don't worry, 110 is extraordinary!
How is Dureene?
Farly severe laceration, but we'll keep
handling her infection.
I'm sure he'll be ok.
Has a scar, and a hell of a story to tell.
If someone believes it, I'm seeing it right now,
and i can't believe it.
You landed a plane on the Hudson without a scratch...
Erny...
The Union is pulling out all the big guns today...
You took a damn risk Sully.
Got a count.
155?
It's official.
Oh, 155.
Thank you Erny.
Hey Carl!
Yes?
Sully.
Carl.
You didn't blown up today, did you?
We're here, that's all I know at the moment.
Oh This is Miss May, from the Hotel.
Would like to have a quick word with you.
This won't take much time gentlemen, this only to say
that our staff is committed to protect your privacy.
If there's something you need, at all...
If it's possible, I'd like to have my uniform cleaned and ready.
Are you kidding?
I'd give you this whole hotel if I could!
Okay, well Thank you Ella.
Thank you very much.
Well, anything for Sully!
What just happened?
You just got hugged by a total stranger.
Ah come on Sully!
When was the last time you heard someone
landing a jetplane on the water?
And finally lived?
Exactly.
I got shaving cream, razor blades, two pairs and some clothes.
Do you think we're ninjas?
It's seven o'clock in the evening.
You find the Merch Brothers!
Yeah.
Sully.
What are you still doing in uniform?
Well, I don't know.
Look guys, it's been a long day.
Why don't you just get some rest?
Mike will be here later to make sure you ok!
Thank you Carl.
No, thank you Captain.
You know, it's been awhile since
New York had news so good.
Especially with airplanes.
I'll see you later Sully.
The word's city officials keep repeating....
And of course the precise timing of the pilot
Captain Sully Sullenbenger, the man who had almost no time
Became a man for all time.
Hey Sully, give me....
Come on, answer...
Larry, the CBR is in 2 days.
How fast can you interfere?
Sully?
I know Airbus has simulations for A320 manifacturer,
but that's next week.
Can you get them to reschedule?
On 3 in the morning?
I need you to make it happen, before
we listen to the CBR.
Before the testimony is complete.
Why?
I have a right to see these simulation, and I have a feeling that with a human pilot
and not a computer, the results would be different.
What if they show the exact same result?
If they do, I'll hang myself in.
It's everything about timing Larry.
You can accomplish anything in a hurry.
Sure as hell I agree with that.
Now the CBR is on Wednesday, that's 36 hours.
Can you make it happen?
I'll try.
I'll give a phone call.
It's already late, so you better get started.
Thank you Larry.
Hey Lory
Hi. I'm sorry bothering you.
Sweetheart, what... What happened?
I just realized that there were 155 people on that plane,
and you were one of them
We almost lost you.
Yeah, but you didn't.
I'm right here.
How are you holding up?
Please tell me that this is almost over.
It's almost over.
Okay.
I love you.
I love you too
I'll call you when they're done with me.
Good Morning Sully.
Alright, Good Morning ladies and Gentlemen.
My name is Charles Porter
I've been assigned from the National Transportation Safety
in order to conduct this hearing today
We have a lot of material to cover.
But before we hear to the cockpit voice recording,
we will listen for the first time with you Gentlemen.
For the request of Captain Sullenberger and the Union,
AirBus has agreed to view pilot simulations.
Upload link, please.
Those simulations Sully, won't change my mind about
what happened up there.
Birds!
Number 1 is on rollback!
Auto-pilot's off.
Pilot off.
Flight director's off.
LaGuardia, due to engine failure, we have to return
Ok, I'm gonna turn left to LaGuardia on 3.
Activated the approach for you.
Activated.
Runway 13
Let's get down nicely.
*ALARM*
Too low.
Succesful landing at La Guardia.
Runway 13
For the record: The pilot's and the computer's simulations made the same result.
Second upload please, about the second run?
Birds.
Give me a heading in 3-1-0
Heading 3-1-0.
1 thousand.
Flaps too
Flaps too.
*ALARM* Too low
Succesful landing, runway 19
Multiple airports, runways, two succesful landings
We are simply seeing what the computer already told us.
A lot of toes  were stepped on
in order to set this up for today.
But frankly, I really don't know
what you gentlemen play the game by.
Can we get serious now?
Captain?
We've all heard about the computer simulations and now
we were watching for actual simulations but
I can't quite believe.
You simply haven't taken into account human factor.
Human pilot simulations showed that
you could have made it back to the airport.
No, they don't.
These pilots were not behaving like human beings.
Like people who were experiencing this for the first time.
But they made up on reacting like you did.
Immediately after the bird strike
they were turning back to the airport.
Correct?
That is correct.
They knew where to turn,
and exactly knew where to fly.
They did not run a check,
they did not turn on the APU
There were all the same paremeters that you faced.
No one warned us.
No one said : You are going to lose both engines
at a lower altitude that any jet in the history.
But be cool, make just a left turn to La Guardia like
you're going back to pick up the milk.
This was a dual engine loss at 2800 feet
followed by immediate water landing. 155 souls on board,
no one ever trained for an incident like that.
No one!
In the TeterBoro landing, with that unrealistick back angle,
we were not to find birds up there.
I'd like to know how many times the pilots practiced that
maneuvre before actually put it off.
I'm not questioning the pilots, they're good pilots.
But they were clearly instructed to head back to the airport
immediately after the bird strike.
You would have no time to analyze this decision.
In these simulations you take
all of the humanity out of the cockpit.
How much time did the pilots had to prepare for this event,
for these simulations?
You were looking for human air.
Then make it human.
This wasn't a videogame.
It was life and death.
Sully's right, that's worth a few seconds.
Please ask practicers how much they had.
17?
The pilot who landed at TeterBoro had 17 practice attempt, before the simulation we just witnessed.
Your reaction-decision time is 35 seconds.
35 seconds is not our time.
We only had 208 second total so....
I'll take it.
Upload link, return to La Guardia.
Now we added 35 seconds to response time.
Birds!
Gas off.
35 seconds.
Time's up.
Here we go.
Going for 13.
We're right ahead for the airport.
*ALARM* Caution, obstacle
We're about 7 miles away.
*ALARM* Terrain! Terrain!
*ALARM* Too low! Terrain!
Let's try Teterboro.
Upload the link please.
Birds!
Flight Director off.
35 seconds.
Engine 1 and 2 fail.
Let's see if we can make it.
Way too low.
*ALARM* Obstacle! Obstacle!
Does anyone need to see any more simulations?
Now that we seen what could have happened,
can we listen at what we actually did?
We will look at other results in another date.
Elizabeth.
For the record, this is the CVR of the Flight 1549,
January 15th, 2009.
Birds!
Shit!
We got one rolling back
We've got both of them rolling back.
Ignition start.
Get out the QRH.
Lost both engines.
Mayday Mayday, we lost both engines,
we're turning to La Guardia.
Okay you need to turn to La Guardia?
Turn left at 220.
Which engine did you loose?
Both, both engines.
Check those flight ignition.
Ignition?
Ignition.
Thrust lighters. Idle?
Idle.
Captain 1549, you want to try land on runway 13?
We are unable,
we're trying to land on the Hudson.
Emergency power. Emergency generators not online.
Not online.
Captain's 1549, it's gonna be runway 31.
Unable
Okay, where do you need to land?
You've got 10 seconds Captain. Talk to me.
Captain 1549, runway 4 is available.
I don't think we can make any runway.
Anything in New Jersey, maybe TeterBoro?
I'll be right side with TeterBoro Airport.
La Guardia Departure? Got an emergency inbound.
Captain 1549, he's going at the airport right now.
You got an emergency?
Yeah, bird strike, Can I get runway 1-1?
Captain 1549, wanna try with Teterboro?
*ALARM* Obstacle, obstacle.
Pull up!
*ALARM* Too low, terrain!
This is the Captain, brace for impact!
Captain 1549 turn right to 3-0.
You can land on 1-0!
We can't make it.
Go ahead and try number 1.
We're going to end up in the Hudson.
All right, let's put the flaps down,
flaps down.
Couple of flaps, want more?
No, it's good.
You got runway 2-9 at Newark,
it's gonna be 2 o'clock, 7 miles.
You got any ideas?
Actually not.
I'd need to take a quick break.
What do they think?
Seeing what I just done?
I'll tell you what I think.
I'm just so damn proud.
You were right there,
With all those distractions.
We did this together like a team.
Thanks Sully.
We did our job.
Alright, we got to get this hearing back to order.
Could you settle please?
Take your seats.
That was honestly,
The first time I was listening to a crash recording.
While actually sitting with the Captain and First Officer.
It's extraordinary.
That was no simulation?
No it wasn't.
Gentlemen, I want to inform you that
the left engine was recovered.
I'll just proceed to a comprehensive report.
There was extensive damage to the fan blades of the engine,
5 compressor blades were fractured.
And 8 aerial veins missing.
So no thrust.
As you testified, it was completely destroyed.
The Aircraft's data was wrong.
I'd like to add something to a personal note:
I can say with absolute confidence that,
After speaking with the rest of the crew
bird experts, aviation engineers,
After running into every scenario,
after running each player,
There were still accidents results..
And it's you, Captain Sullenberger, removing you from
the equation of math, just fails.
I disagree.
It wasn't just me, it was all of us.
Jeff, Donna, Shila and Dureene.
And all passengers, rescue workers.
And Traffic Control,
Helicopter Crews and Scuba Cops.
We all did it!
We survived.
First Officer Skiles,
Is there anything you'd like to add?
Anything you would have done different,
If you had to do it again?
Yes, I would have done it in July!
Subs by Sergeddu